RUTVIK MORADIYA

IOS DEVELOPER

Email: rutvikmoradiya0811@gmail.com

Phone: +91 90163 50937

ABOUT

I am writing to apply for an iOS Developer position. I am hardworking, passionate, and eager to learn new things. I have experience in understanding Apple's design principles and interface guidelines to implement in iOS apps.

With almost 3 years of experience as an iOS Developer, I have a proven track record of success in this field. I have developed and released several successful apps that have received critical acclaim. I am also well-versed in the latest trends and technologies in the iOS Development industry, and I am confident that I can quickly adapt to your team's needs.

SKILLS

- iPhone and iPad app development
- Xcode
- Objective C, Swift
- Firebase, SQLite, Core Database
- Push and Local Notification
- Team Collaboration
- Github, Sourcetree
- App Deployment
- Familiarity with HTTP, and RESTful APIs for connection with iOS app backend server Remote database.
- Experience with third-party libraries and APIs.
- Expertise in building complex layouts with UIKit.
- Experience working with iOS frameworks such as CoreData, AVKit, AVFoundation, StoreKit, CoreAnimation, AudioToolbox, WebKit, MapKit, and many more.
- Core Animation, NFC Reader, Social Integration, In-App Purchase, and Advertising.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER APPLICATION

Veer Narmad South Gujarat University, Surat, Gujarat. June 2017 - March 2021

EXPERIENCE

IOS DEVELOPER

• Worked from August 2021 to December 2022 at Samp Solution.

IOS DEVELOPER

• Worked from January 2023 to February 2024 at Uptechies.

AZILLIK IT SOLUTION

• Currently, I have been working as a Senior IOS Developer at Azillik IT Solution since March 2024.

CAREER OBJECTIVE

• To associate myself with an organization, with all dedication, honesty & integrity while contributing to the growth of the organization to the best of my ability.

STRENGTHS

- Quick learner and Good communication skills.
- Ready to take Responsibility.

PORTFOLIO:

WEIGHT TRACK & MONITOR



JSU RIDE



• PARQ - DIGITAL VALET TICKET



 TRANSCENDING MANTRA:MEDITATE



QALBYAPP



PTCB PRACTICE TEST PREP

